<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Hermosa Beach Pack 860]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Hermosa Beach Pack 860]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/pack860hb/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 03:04:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/pack860hb/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 03:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to the Adventure of Scouting!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2>Welcome to the Adventure of Scouting!</h2>,<p>Pack 860 is a chartered Cub Scout affiliate of the Boy Scouts of America sponsored by the Hermosa Beach Rotary Club. We strive to enrich each boy’s life with purpose and values that reflect the ideals of Scouting and the idyllic Hermosa Beach lifestyle. We weave fun, education, adventure and age appropriate responsibility into a tapestry of group and individual achievements that serve the Community, Pack and individual. Each scout is empowered to develop, create, achieve and learn via the time honored traditions of the Boy Scouts of America.</p>,<p>But mostly Cub Scouts is FUN! Den meetings, campouts, pack meetings, pinewood derby races and so many more activities that inspire, entertain and teach. Pack 860 laughs, learns and explores like no other.</p>,<p>We are a 100% non-profit, volunteer run organization that prides itself on maintaining the highest standards of safety and excellence for each and every member. Our leadership is trained and certified by the BSA.</p>,<p>To learn more, <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfsyb7MamLVRMVXkgEhgajQCJDygNzzWWhqPGEhHmbvXYISAg/viewform?usp=sf_link" title="New Scout Inquiry Form">please fill out this webform.</a> Your privacy is rigorously protected and we will NOT contact you without permission.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f7fc2bcc-bf43-4380-b22c-45d166d40f02.jpg" title="Build Friends that last a lifetime.">,<p>You may also visit Pack 860 <a href="https://scoutlander.com/publicsite/unithome.aspx?UID=19278" title="Pack 860 Scoutlander page">on Scoutlander.com</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/pack860hb/welcome-to-the-adventure-of-scouting/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">452e9070-f7fd-4bf0-a4a6-6f1210151281</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 20:45:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>